AFSCME, District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004.
  - Subseries IV:B: Bill Schleicher Records, 1992-2004.
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) Dispute: People of the State of New York v. Charles Hughes and Mildred Stephens, ca.1999 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) Dispute: People of the State of New York v. Martin Hughes, Joseph Alfano, James Rose, and Richard Lewis, ca.1999 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Local 375 (CSTG) Dispute: CSTG v. DC 37, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Urban Park Rangers Retirement Program, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Local Presidents: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Medicaid Budget Cuts, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Meeting Notes, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 2003 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - New York State AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Officer Structure, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Per Diem Employees, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Pinkett, Mary: Death of, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Political Action, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Bush v. Kerry), 2004 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Press Releases, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Rallies: Meeting Notes, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Reagan, Ronald: Death of, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Republican National Convention Protests, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Roberts, Lillian: Re-Election of, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Shop Stewards: Meeting Notes, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Staff: Meeting Notes, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Telephone Directory, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Subseries IV:C: Public Employee Press Research Files, 1963-1993.
    - Anti-Ballistic Missile System (ABM), 1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Blue Collar Locals: Citywide Strike, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Clippings: State Civil Service Eployees Association (CSEA) Strike, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: General, undated; 1963; 1970-1995 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Education Conference, 1963, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Event Programs and Announcements, undated, 1973-1978, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Hospital Exposé, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Exposé, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Hospital Exposé: Bellevue Hospital, 1965-1971 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Hospital Exposé: Kings County Hospital, 1967-1972 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Hospital Exposé: Lincoln Hospital, 1966-1972 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Interview Notes: Members of Locals 372, 376, 384, 1113, 1407, 1501, 1502, 1549, 1597, and 2021, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Leadership Conference, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1973-1980 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Education Conferences, 1982, 1987, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, UFT Challenge, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Hospital Strike, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Nurse's Aides Upgrading Program, 1966-1970 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Service Awards, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Local 1087 (Prevailing Rate Employees): Radio Repair Mechanics, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Local 1795 (Stationary Firemen): Safety Issues, 1970-1976, 1982, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 1967-1972 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals I, 1967-1968, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals II, 1967-1968, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Notes, undated (Box 43a, Folder 1)
    - Paycheck Cashing: Joseph Sperling v. Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company, 1976 (Box 43a, Folder 2)
    - Political Action: Goldberg-Paterson Campaign (Opposition to AFL-CIO Rockefeller Endorsement), 1970 (Box 43a, Folder 3)
    - Safety Committee Inspections, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Substance Abuse Conference, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Taylor Law: Madison Square Garden Rally, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Taylor Law: Response to Sanitation and Teachers' Strikes, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000.
  - Agreement: DC 37 and AFSCME, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Agreement: New York State Federation of Labor and New York State Industrial Union Council, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO: Membership Education and Mobilization for Organizing Manual, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME: Affiliation Agreement with Lassen County Employees Association, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME: Employees' Pension Plan, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME: Financial Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME: Secretary-Treasurer Educational Workshop, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME: Trust Agreement with National Bank of Washington, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - AFSCME, Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAE), Local 1707, 1958-1963 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME, CSAE, Local 1707, 1964-1967 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - AFSCME, CSAE, Local 1707: Contested Election of Delegates to AFSCME Convention, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME, Council 50, 1967-1969 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME, Council 50: Mental Hospital Strike-- Clippings, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME, Council 62, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME Employees Federal Credit Union, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th), 1958 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th): Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th) (Oversize), 1958 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME International Convention (16th), 1966 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Agendas, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Minutes, 1968, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files I, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files II, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files III, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - AFSCME Legislation Department, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - AFSCME Task Force for the Future, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Benefit Fund, 1958-1965 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Blue Collar Division: Leaflets, 1970-1972 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Chaplains Organizing Committee, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Employees, 1972, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Citywide Contract, 1967, 1970-1976, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Clerical Division: Citywide Organizing Materials, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Clerical-Administrative Division: Leaflets, 1970-1972 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Clippings: General, 1967-1987, 1991-1998, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining: Citywide Agreement Impasse, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Union Responsibility (COUR), 1961, 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Community School Board, District 1 Elections, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: General, 1955-1956 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: General, 1957-1958 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan 1959-Jun 1959 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul 1959-Dec 1959 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan 1960-Jun 1960 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul 1960-1962; 1968-1977; 1986 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Delegate Calculations, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 Charter, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - DC 37: General/History, 1944-1945, 1965-1972, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Education Fund, 1970-1976 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Education Fund, undated, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Fiscal Crisis, 1970, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Forms: General, 1970s (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Grievance Procedures and Collective Bargaining Manual, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Health and Security Plan, 1970-1976, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Health News Daily, Jun 1996-Sep 1996 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Health News Daily, Sep 1996-Dec 1996 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Health News Daily, Dec 1996-Feb 1997 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Health News Daily, Feb 1997-Apr 1997 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Health News Daily, Apr 1997-Jun 1997 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Health News Daily, Jun 1997-Jul 1997 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Hospitals--Strikes: Clippings, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Hospitals Division: Leaflets, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Housing Division: Organizing Materials, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Irish Heritage, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Leaflets: General, 1962-1966; 1970-1976; 1981 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Leaflets: Other Organizations, 1967-1968; 1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Leaflets: Social and Political Issues, 1964, 1971-1976 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets: Social and Political Issues, 1982; 1987 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Legislation (Public Health), 1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Local 135B (Brooklyn Museum) and 135M (Metropolitan Museum of Art), 1956 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks), 1955-1966 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks): Grievances, 1956-1965 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks): Meeting Notices, 1958-1966 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Local 154 (NYC Amalgamated Professional Employees), 1963-1966, 1972-1974, ca.1982 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Local 188 (Municipal Examiners and Analysts), 1967 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1953-1959 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1960-1963 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1964-1967 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), undated, 1970-1976, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Assistant Supervisors of Recreation (Oversize), 1963 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Baron v. Morris Case, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Grievances, 1956-1966 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Jimmy Carosella, 1990-1993 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Meeting Notices and Printed Material, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Newsletters, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Local 322 (Uniformed Sanitation Men), 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Local 371 (Social Service Employees Union, SSEU), 1958-1962 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jan 1965-Jun 1965 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jul 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jan 1966-Jun 1966 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jul 1966-Dec 1966 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), 1967, 1973, 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Certification Amendment, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Children's Shelters, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Collective Bargaining, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Constitution and Bylaws, undated, 1961-1964 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Grievances, 1956-1961 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Grievances, 1963-1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Manual of Operations and Forms, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Jan 1965-Jun 1965 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Jul 1965-Apr 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Newsletters and Bulletins, 1963-1969; 1984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Printed Material, 1962-1966, 1970-1976, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1962-1966 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): SSEU Election and Strike, 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): SSEU Printed Material, 1963-1966 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Budget Crisis, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike I, 1964-1966 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike II, 1964-1966 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike (Oversize), 1965 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Bulletins, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Captain Reports, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Report, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Agreements, 1974-1976; 1980-1982 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Constitution, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Family Paraprofessionals, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, 1957-1963, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, Grievances, 1957-1965 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, Meeting Notices, 1961-1963 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Minutes, 1963-1966, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Newsletters, 1965-1966, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Policy Consultation Council, 1956-1966 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Policy Consultation Council, Minutes, 1957-1965 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Printed Material, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Printed Material, 1975-1977; 1981-1982; 1988 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, 1963-1966, 1971-1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, Grievances, 1964-1966; 1975; 1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, Salary Appeal Briefs, 1965-1966 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, UFT Challenge, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1958-1961 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Jan 1965-Jun 1965 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Jul 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1966, 1973-1980 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1957-1961 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1963-1966, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Salary Appeal Briefs, 1958-1962 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Program Assistants, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees), 1961-1965, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Agreements, 1958-1965 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, 1956-Apr 1959 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, May 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, 1961-1965 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Grievances, 1958-1965 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1961-1966 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, 1957-1966, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Job Descriptions, 1961-1965 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Staff Committee Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Staff News, 1960-1964 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1966 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Local 375 (Civil Service Technical Guild, CSTG), 1957-1958 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1959-1961 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1965-1967, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1982, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 3, Department of Hospitals, undated, 1963-1967, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 10, Department of Health, 1964-1967 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 13, Board of Water Supply, 1965-1967 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 14, Board of Education, 1963-1967 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 17, Department of Buildings, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 38, Housing and Redevelopment Board, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Department of Hospitals, City Civil Service Commission Public Hearing Transcript, Mar 27, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Fire Prevention Inspectors, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Grievances, 1957-1965 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Minutes, 1957-1963, 1965, 1970-1975 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Newsletters, 1964-1976, 1982, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Printed Material, 1970-1976, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Salary Appeal Briefs and Reallocations, 1957-1967 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Local 376 (Construction Laborers, Highway Repairers, and Watershed Maintainers), 1966-1975, 1980-1982, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers), 1956-1962 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Constitution, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Legislative Issues, 1953-1957 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Minutes, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Local 381 (Association of Laboratory Teachers), 1960-1962 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Local 384 (Board of Higher Education), 1966, 1972-1976, 1980-1982 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1955-1959 1961 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1962 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), undated, 1963-1966, 1972-1979 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Grievances, 1955-1964 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Hospital Strike, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Laundry Workers Organizing, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1955-1966 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Newsletters, 1964-1966 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Practical Nurses Organizing, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Printed Material, 1970-1976, 1981-1984 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Salary Appeal Briefs, ca.1955-1962 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Local 436 (United Federation of Nurses), 1970-1976, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Local 461 (Lifeguards), 1963-1967 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Local 663 (New Rochelle Employees), 1965-1968 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Local 663 (New Rochelle Employees): Minutes, Union-City Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees, formerly Local 154W), 1955-1967 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees), 1970-1976, 1982, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Cleaners (formerly Local 154W), Grievances, 1956-1958 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Cleaners, Meeting Notices and Newsletters, undated, 1961-1966 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Clerical-Administrative Employees, 1954-1967 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Clerical-Administrative Employees, Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1959-1967 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Constitution, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Dental Hygienists, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Exterminators, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Laboratory Helpers, 1955-1957 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Laboratory Helpers, Grievances, 1955-1959 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Materials I, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Materials II, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Notes I, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Notes II, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, 1955-1964, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees) Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Grievances, 1955-1965 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Job Duties Questionnaires, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1960-1966 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Minutes, 1958-1964 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, 1956-1959, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Certification Dispute with New York State Nurses' Association, 1958-1959 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Grievances, 1956-1960 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Meeting Notices, 1959-1963; 1991 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Printed Material, ca.1957 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, 1953-1957 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, 1958-1967 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, Grievances, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)